Guide to the Dick Thornburgh Papers, 1932- AIS.1998.30.10
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Re-election Campaign for Governor, 1982; X.
  - Opposition Research, Ertel and Lloyd, 6.
    - Allen Ertel (D), Governor
      - Research Binders
        - Research binder annotated by Thornburgh, Volume 2: Human Service issues and constituencies, Miscellaneous, Lloyd, Appendices, 1982 (Box 133, Folder 5-6)
      - Major Issues
        - Integrity in government, 1982 (Box 133, Folder 7)
        - Budget and taxes, 1977-1980 (Box 133, Folder 8-9)
        - Size and efficiency in government, 1978-1982 (Box 133, Folder 10)
        - Economic development, 1980-1982 (Box 133, Folder 11-17)
        - Economic development, 1980-1982 (Box 134, Folder 1-2)
        - Transportation, 1977-1982 (Box 134, Folder 3-4)
        - Education, March-October, 1982 (Box 134, Folder 5-6)
        - Crime, 1977-1982 (Box 134, Folder 7-8)
        - Human services, 1982 (Box 134, Folder 9)
        - Human services: health and welfare backup, 1977-1980 (Box 134, Folder 10)
        - Human services: health, 1982 (Box 134, Folder 11)
        - Human services: welfare reform, March-September, 1982 (Box 134, Folder 12)
        - Human services: aging, March, 1982 (Box 134, Folder 13)
        - Energy and environment, 1977-1982 (Box 134, Folder 14-15)
        - Three Mile Island (TMI): research binder backup references, 1980-1982 (Box 134, Folder 16)
        - Three Mile Island (TMI): opposition research on Allen Ertel and Three Mile Island (TMI), 1978-1982 (Box 134, Folder 17)
        - Three Mile Island (TMI): Allen Ertel testimony before Energy, Conservation and Power, May 1, 1982 (Box 134, Folder 18)
        - Three Mile Island (TMI): memos and correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box 134, Folder 19)
        - Three Mile Island (TMI): press releases, Congressional Record, and analyses, 1982 (Box 134, Folder 20)
        - Three Mile Island (TMI): clippings, May, 1979-July, 1982 (Box 134, Folder 21)
        - Liquor reform, 1982 (Box 134, Folder 22)
      - Constituencies
        - Blacks: opposition research binder backup references, 1977-1982 (Box 134, Folder 23-24)
        - Ethnics and other minorities, 1980-1982 (Box 134, Folder 25)
        - Women, 1977-1982 (Box 134, Folder 26)
        - Senior citizens, 1977-1982 (Box 135, Folder 1)
        - Farmers, 1977-1982 (Box 135, Folder 2-3)
        - Veterans, 1980-1982 (Box 135, Folder 4)
        - Sportsmen, 1982 (Box 135, Folder 5)
        - Labor, 1976-1982 (Box 135, Folder 6-7)
        - Business, 1978-1982 (Box 135, Folder 8)
        - Firefighters, 1978-1982 (Box 135, Folder 9)
        - Religion, 1980 (Box 135, Folder 10)
        - Local government and housing, 1982 (Box 135, Folder 11)
        - Consumer, July-August, 1982 (Box 135, Folder 12)
        - Office of Employment Statistics (OES), August-September, 1982 (Box 135, Folder 13)
      - Miscellaneous Issues
        - Abortion, February-July, 1982 (Box 135, Folder 14)
        - Defense: National security, 1978-1982 (Box 135, Folder 15)
        - Foreign relations, 1978-1982 (Box 135, Folder 16)
        - Federal, state, local relations (including Federalism, federal budget, and Federal Dollars for Pennsylvania), 1980 (Box 135, Folder 17)
        - Consumerism, March-April, 1982 (Box 135, Folder 18)
        - Centralia, 1981-1982 (Box 135, Folder 19)
        - Ertel on the Issues, general, 1978-1982 (Box 135, Folder 20)
      - Personal History
        - Biographies, 1982 (Box 135, Folder 21)
        - Family, 1982 (Box 135, Folder 22)
        - Friends, 1982 (Box 135, Folder 23)
        - District Attorney elections, March-November, 1976 (Box 135, Folder 24)
        - District Attorney performance, 1982 (Box 135, Folder 25)
        - Legal practice, 1976 (Box 135, Folder 26)
      - Congressional Record
        - Congressional elections: Allen Ertel campaign material, and clippings, 1976-1980 (Box 135, Folder 27)
        - Congressional elections: Rippon clippings, 1978 (Box 135, Folder 28)
        - Congressional performance and voting records: memos and correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 135, Folder 29)
        - Congressional performance and voting records: ratings, and key votes, 1977-1982 (Box 136, Folder 1)
        - Congressional performance and voting records: voter groups ratings (Congressional Quarterly), 1977-1982 (Box 136, Folder 2)
        - Congressional performance and voting records: flood control legislation clippings, 1978-1982 (Box 136, Folder 3)
        - Congressional performance and voting records: clippings, 1976-1982 (Box 136, Folder 4)
        - Congressional performance and voting records: House roll-call votes, 1977-1982 (Box 136, Folder 5-10)
        - Congressional performance and voting records: House roll-call votes, business and labor, 1977-1980 (Box 136, Folder 11)
        - Congressional performance and voting records: House roll-call votes, Congress and the government, 1977-1980 (Box 136, Folder 12)
        - Congressional performance and voting records: House roll-call votes, defense and foreign policy, 1977-1980 (Box 136, Folder 13)
        - Congressional performance and voting records: House roll-call votes, domestic affairs, 1977-1980 (Box 137, Folder 1)
        - Congressional performance and voting records: House roll-call votes, economy and budget, 1977-1980 (Box 137, Folder 2)
        - Congressional performance and voting records: House roll-call votes, energy and the environment, 1977-1980 (Box 137, Folder 3)
        - Congressional performance and voting records: Congressional Record binders, 1977-1982 (Box 137, Folder 4-9)
        - Congressional performance and voting records: Congressional Record, arranged by topics, 1977-1982 (Box 137, Folder 10)
        - Congressional Quarterly, 1982 (Box 138, Folder 1)
        - Associations, memberships, and awards, 1977-1982 (Box 138, Folder 2)
        - Contributors, 1976-1980 (Box 138, Folder 3)
        - Personal finances, 1974-1981 (Box 138, Folder 4)
        - Expenses in office, 1977-1981 (Box 138, Folder 5)
        - Employees, 1976-1982 (Box 138, Folder 6)
        - Foreign travel, 1977-1981 (Box 138, Folder 7)
        - Media relations, 1981-1982 (Box 138, Folder 8)
        - Personality, 1982 (Box 138, Folder 9)
      - 1982 Campaign
        - Announcement, February, 1982 (Box 138, Folder 10)
        - Campaign contributors and campaign expense reports, January 1, 1982-October 18, 1982 (Box 138, Folder 11-12)
        - Campaign expenses, 1980-1982 (Box 138, Folder 13)
        - Campaign staff, 1982 (Box 138, Folder 14)
        - Campaign supporters, 1972-1982 (Box 138, Folder 15)
        - Campaign supporters: endorsements, 1982 (Box 139, Folder 1)
        - Campaign supporters: Shapp-related, 1980-1982 (Box 139, Folder 2)
        - Campaign supporters: other, 1982 (Box 139, Folder 3)
        - Campaign supporters: Republicans for Ertel, 1980-1982 (Box 139, Folder 4)
        - Campaign supporters: parallel to Governor leader, 1982 (Box 139, Folder 5)
        - Campaign detractors, 1982 (Box 139, Folder 6)
        - Campaign scheduling events (past/present/future/debate), 1982 (Box 139, Folder 7)
        - Mailings: franking, 1980-1982 (Box 139, Folder 8)
        - Poll results, 1982 (Box 139, Folder 9)
        - Press releases, 1982 (Box 139, Folder 10-11)
        - Misrepresentations (1982 campaign and prior), 1979-1982 (Box 139, Folder 12)
        - Campaign organization, 1978-1982 (Box 139, Folder 13-14)
        - Schedules, September-October, 1982 (Box 139, Folder 15)
        - Position papers, 1982 (Box 139, Folder 16)
        - Media spots, May-August, 1982 (Box 139, Folder 17)
        - Public appearance transcripts, June-October, 1982 (Box 139, Folder 18)
        - Correspondence, May-October, 1982 (Box 139, Folder 19)
        - Airplane Issue, July, 1977-September, 1982 (Box 139, Folder 20)
        - Ertel handouts, 1982 (Box 139, Folder 21)
        - Ertel record, 1981-1982 (Box 139, Folder 22)
        - Negative clippings, July-October, 1982 (Box 139, Folder 23)
        - Lloyd clippings, 1979-1982 (Box 140, Folder 1)
        - Ertel clippings, 1967-1981 (Box 140, Folder 2-9)
        - Binder: Sunbury Daily Item clippings, 1980-1982 (Box 140, Folder 10)
        - Binder: Allen Ertel Congressional Record, 1977-1980 (Box 140, Folder 11)
        - Binder: Sunbury Daily Item, clippings, 1967-1977 (Box 140, Folder 12-13)
        - Binder: Williamsport Sun Gazette, clippings, 1978-1981 (Box 140, Folder 14-15)
    - James Lloyd (D), Lieutenant Governor
      - Issues
        - Lloyd bullets, May-October, 1982 (Box 141, Folder 1)
        - Integrity in government, 1980 (Box 141, Folder 2)
        - Budget and taxes, 1981-1982 (Box 141, Folder 3)
        - Size and efficiency in government, 1981-1982 (Box 141, Folder 4)
        - Economic development, 1979-1982 (Box 141, Folder 5-7)
        - Transportation, 1979-1982 (Box 141, Folder 8)
        - Education, 1979-1982 (Box 141, Folder 9)
        - Human services: welfare reform, 1979-1982 (Box 141, Folder 10)
        - Human services: aging, 1979-1982 (Box 141, Folder 11)
        - Abortion, 1979-1982 (Box 141, Folder 12)
      - Personal and Legislative History
        - Biography, 1979 (Box 141, Folder 13)
        - Senate voting record: memos and analyses, 1979-1982 (Box 141, Folder 14)
        - Senate voting record: missed votes, 1979-1982 (Box 141, Folder 15)
        - Senate voting record: Legislative journal, Senate, 1979-1982 (Box 141, Folder 16-19)
      - 1982 Campaign
        - Announcement: Gubernatorial announcement, January, 1982 (Box 141, Folder 20)
        - Announcement: media monitoring, 1982 (Box 141, Folder 21)
        - Campaign expenses, 1980-1982 (Box 141, Folder 22)
        - Campaign schedules, 1982 (Box 141, Folder 23)
        - Correspondence (including from Governor Thornburgh), 1980-1982 (Box 141, Folder 24)
        - Clippings, January-October, 1982 (Box 141, Folder 25)
        - Miscellaneous memos and campaign issue material, 1982 (Box 141, Folder 26)
  - Campaign in Progress, 7.
    These files are the major and inclusive working files of the Governor Thornburgh Committee, or GTC that led the Thornburgh-Scranton re-election bid in 1982. These files contain staff memos and correspondence, organizational information, fundraising and finances information, voter groups and county files, speeches, and volunteer information. The extensive sections including endorsements and questionnaires are particularly interesting. They give us a clear picture of both the organizations and persons supporting Thornburgh-Scranton a second time, as well as a succinct summary of the candidates' responses on key issues. The endorsements and questionnaires are organized chronologically and alphabetically. All binder material has been entitled as such, referencing the original order, but has been placed in folders for preservation purposes. Also here are Ginny Thornburgh's campaign files, as she once again was a loyal and devoted campaign voice on her husband's behalf.
    The sixteen sections are as follows: Staff List and Memoranda; Correspondence; Miscellaneous Campaign Files; Organization; County Files; Fundraising; Voter Groups; Endorsements; Speeches; Questionnaires and Responses; Debate Issue; Controversies and Critics; Volunteers and Phone Banks; Ginny Thornburgh's Files; Ephemera; Volunteer Printout.
    - Staff Lists and Memoranda
      - Campaign staff lists, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 1)
      - Memos: Waldman, 1981-1983 (Box 142, Folder 2)
      - Memos: Asher and Brownell, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 3)
      - Memos: Critchlow, July 6, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 4)
      - Memos: Dunkle, March 8, 1982-December 28, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 5)
      - Memos: Meloy, July 29, 1982-October 22, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 6)
      - Memos: Phenicie, September 29, 1982-November 9, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence
      - General correspondence and Thornburgh notes, August 13, 1982-November 3, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 8)
      - Asher, March 24, 1982-October 13, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 9)
      - Asher incoming, January 25, 1982-December 31, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 10)
      - Dunkle, January 18, 1982-October 29, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 11)
      - Asher/Dunkle field, July 12-23, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 12)
      - Hoffman, May 13, 1982-October 1, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 13)
      - Governor Thornburgh, February 22, 1982-November 21, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 14)
      - Governor Thornburgh to Legislative candidates, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 15)
      - Governor Thornburgh greetings, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 16)
      - Committee correspondence, fundraising, general instructions and schedules, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous Campaign Files
      - Budget, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 18)
      - Forms and instructions, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 19)
      - Stationery, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 20)
      - Offers to help, February 6, 1981-October 15, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 21)
      - Pennsylvania Republican leaders, 1981-1982 (Box 142, Folder 22)
      - Published articles, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 23)
      - Miscellaneous: PSEA letter, The Baron Report, and media time listings, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 24)
      - Press releases: miscellaneous, March-April, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 25)
      - Legislative photo sessions, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 26)
    - Organization
      - Regional field representatives, July-August, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 27)
      - Regional field representatives: Anne Anstine, January-April, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 28)
      - Regional field representatives: Richard Bartlett, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 29)
      - Regional field representatives: Jean Kistler, April-August, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 30)
      - Regional field representatives: Patricia Raugh, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 31)
      - Western region counties, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 32)
      - Western region regional coordinators, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 33)
      - Western region regional coordinators: Syed Ali-Zaidi, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 34)
      - Western region regional coordinators: George Loranger, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 35)
      - Western region regional coordinators: Philip English, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 36)
      - Western region regional coordinators: Thomas Murray, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 1)
      - Western region county coordinators, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 2)
      - Western region field meetings, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 3)
      - Western region office (Meloy): outgoing correspondence, 1977-1982 (Box 143, Folder 4-7)
      - Western Pennsylvania rally, October 27, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 8)
      - Coordinators' seminar, April 24, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 9)
    - County Files
      - County coordinators, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 10)
      - County budget list, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 11)
      - County coordinators' meetings, July 16, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 12)
      - County coordinators' handouts, 1981-1982 (Box 143, Folder 13)
      - Adams, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 14)
      - Allegheny, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 15)
      - Armstrong, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 16)
      - Beaver, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 17)
      - Bedford, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 18)
      - Berks, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 19)
      - Blair, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 20)
      - Bradford, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 21)
      - Bucks, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 22)
      - Butler, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 23)
      - Cambria, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 24)
      - Cameron, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 25)
      - Carbon, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 26)
      - Centre, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 27)
      - Chester, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 28)
      - Clarion, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 29)
      - Clearfield, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 30)
      - Clinton, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 31)
      - Columbia, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 32)
      - Crawford, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 33)
      - Cumberland, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 34)
      - Dauphin, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 35)
      - Delaware, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 36)
      - Elk, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 37)
      - Erie, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 38)
      - Fayette, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 39)
      - Forest, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 40)
      - Franklin, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 41)
      - Fulton, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 42)
      - Greene, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 43)
      - Huntingdon, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 44)
      - Indiana, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 45)
      - Jefferson, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 46)
      - Juniata, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 47)
      - Lackawanna, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 48)
      - Lancaster, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 49)
      - Lawrence, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 50)
      - Lebanon, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 51)
      - Lehigh, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 52)
      - Luzerne, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 53)
      - Lycoming, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 54)
      - McKean, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 55)
      - Mercer, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 56)
      - Mifflin, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 57)
      - Monroe, 1982 (Box 143, Folder 58)
      - Montgomery, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 1)
      - Montour, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 2)
      - Northampton, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 3)
      - Northumberland, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 4)
      - Perry, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 5)
      - Philadelphia, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 6)
      - Pike, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 7)
      - Potter, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 8)
      - Schuylkill, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 9)
      - Snyder, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 10)
      - Somerset, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 11)
      - Sullivan, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 12)
      - Susquehanna, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 13)
      - Tioga, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 14)
      - Union, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 15)
      - Venango, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 16)
      - Warren, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 17)
      - Washington, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 18)
      - Wayne, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 19)
      - Westmoreland, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 20)
      - Wyoming, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 21)
      - York, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 22)
    - Fundraising
      - Treasurer authorization and campaign expense statements, 1981-1982 (Box 144, Folder 23)
      - Fundraising mailings, 1981-1982 (Box 144, Folder 24)
      - Fundraiser proposal form, 1981-1982 (Box 144, Folder 25)
      - Major fundraisers, 1981-1982 (Box 144, Folder 26)
      - Other fundraisers, 1981-1982 (Box 144, Folder 27)
      - Campaign contributions procedures, 1981-1982 (Box 144, Folder 28)
      - Campaign contributions lists, 1981-1982 (Box 144, Folder 29-30)
      - Seif and Ethics Commission: transcript of interview regarding use of Governor's Home for fundraising, March 17, 1983 (Box 144, Folder 31)
    - Voter Groups
      - Plans, strategy and voter opinion analysis (AFSCME), 1982 (Box 144, Folder 32)
      - Mailings and status reports, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 33)
      - Miscellaneous: PSEA letter, The Baron Report, and media time listings, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 34)
    - Endorsements
      - Non Philadelphia or Pittsburgh endorsements, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 35)
      - Endorsement lists, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 36)
      - Albion News, October 27, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 37)
      - Allegheny County Republican Heritage Groups, June 14, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 38)
      - Altoona Mirror, October 30, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 39)
      - Ardmore Main Line Times, October 28, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 40)
      - Association of Pennsylvania State College and University Faculties, October 7, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 41)
      - Athletes for Thornburgh/Scranton Committee, October 14, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 42)
      - Atlantic Apparel Contractors Association, July 20, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 43)
      - Boilermakers Local No. 154, Fred Gualtieri, business manager, March 2, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 44)
      - Beaver County Times, October 29, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 45)
      - Bowser, John, former executive director, Urban Coalition, October 22, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 46)
      - Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades, Scotty Campbell, secretary/treasurer, August 9, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 47)
      - Bucks County Courier Times, October 25, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 48)
      - Business for Thornburgh/Scranton Committees: Concerned Business People for Thornburgh/Scranton, September, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 49)
      - Business for Thornburgh/Scranton Committees: Small Business for Thornburgh/Scranton Committee, September, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 50)
      - Centre Daily Times, October 24, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 51)
      - Chester, Delaware County Daily Times, October 26, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 52)
      - Democrats for Thornburgh-Scranton Committee, September 22, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 53)
      - Doylestown Daily Intelligencer, October 29, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 54)
      - Dykes, John, business manager, Streetcleaners Local 427, February 25, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 55)
      - Educators for Thornburgh-Scranton Committee, May 24, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 56)
      - Educators for Thornburgh-Scranton Committee: Basic Education, May 27, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 57)
      - Educators for Thornburgh-Scranton Committee: Higher Education, June 9, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 58)
      - Educators for Thornburgh-Scranton Committee: Retired Educators, October, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 59)
      - Erie Metro Times-News, October 31, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 60)
      - Erie Times-News, October 24, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 61)
      - Evans, Samuel, chairman of Family of Leaders, September 16, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 62)
      - Family of Leaders Executive Committee, September 16, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 63)
      - Farmers for Thornburgh-Scranton Committee, July 8, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 64)
      - Fireman's Association of Pennsylvania, July 8, 1982; September 11, 1982 (Box 144, Folder 65)
      - Fireman's Legislative Federation of Pennsylvania, June 26, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 1)
      - Fondy, Albert, president, Pittsburgh Federation of Teachers, September 7, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 2)
      - Fraternal Order of Police, Pennsylvania Lodge, September 7, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 3)
      - Fraternal Order of Police, Philadelphia Lodge, No. 5, September 23, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 4)
      - Friends and Family of Three Mile Island (TMI), May 19, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 5)
      - Greensburg Tribune Review, October 24, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 6)
      - Hanover Evening Sun, October 29, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 7)
      - Harrisburg Patriot-News, October 17, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 8)
      - Harrisburg PA Beacon, October 27, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 9)
      - Hatboro Today's Spirit, October 25, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 10)
      - Hispanic-American Council, Inc. of Erie, March 3, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 11)
      - Indiana Gazette, October 28, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 12)
      - International Longshoremen's Local No. 1291, Alex Talmadge, president, February 25, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 13)
      - Jackson, Reverend Jesse, October 22, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 14)
      - Jenkintown Globe, October 28, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 15)
      - Jenkintown Montgomery County Record, October 26, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 16)
      - Jenkintown Times Chronicle, October 28, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 17)
      - Johnstown Tribune-Democrat, October 17, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 18)
      - Keystone State Chapter of the International Society of Fire Service Instructors, April 17, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 19)
      - Keystone State Fire Chiefs Association, May 15, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 20)
      - Lancaster New Era, October 15, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 21)
      - Lebanon Sunday Pennsylvanian, October 24, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 22)
      - Lewistown Sentinel, October 21, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 23)
      - Love, Ruth, columnist, October 31, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 24)
      - Milton Standard, October 29, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 25)
      - National Rifle Association, Institute for Legislative Action, October 27, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 26)
      - National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, Henry Nicholas, president, October 15, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 27)
      - Oreland Springfield Sun, October 28, 1982 (Box 145, Folder 28)